1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
41. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
45. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
53. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
61. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
65. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn_checkout"))
69. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
73. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
77. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
81. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), 10)
85. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
89. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
93. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), randomAddress)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
105. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Province"))
109. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Select Province"))
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_Districts"))
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-save"))
133. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-change"), 2)
137. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-change"), 6)
141. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-change"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
145. takeScreenshot()
149. updateAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
153. updateCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
157. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), 10)
161. clearText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"))
165. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/field_Address"), updateAddress)
169. clearText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"))
173. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/input_ZipPostal Code"), updateCode)
177. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-save"))
181. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-change"), 2)
185. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Address Ship To/btn-change"), 10)
189. takeScreenshot()
193. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
197. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
201. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
205. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
209. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
213. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
217. comment("Updated Address : " + updateAddress)
221. comment("Updated Code    : " + updateCode)
225. closeBrowser()